birthdaywishes.expert 2018-12-11

# Privacy Policy of Birthday Wishes Expert

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@birthdaywishes.expert

Birthday Wishes

Quotes

Good Morning

People

### **1\. Introduction**

Thanks for visiting Birthday Wishes Expert. This website was designed to provide wishes, quotes and inspiration for everyday human activities.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the www.birthdaywishes.expert website.

BY ACCESSING AND USING THIS WEBSITE OR BY DOWNLOADING ANY MATERIAL (FILES, IMAGES, SOUNDS, etc,), YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES OUTLINED IN AND AGREE TO GIVE YOUR CONSENT TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY. IF ANY OF THE TERMS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS SOMETHING YOU DISAGREE WITH, PLEASE EXERCISE YOUR RIGHT AS A FREE INTERNET USER BY LEAVING THIS WEBSITE.

### **2\. Our Commitment to Privacy**

Here at Birthday Wishes Expert your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

In order to make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### **3\. Personal Information We Collect:**

If you are a registered user of the Birthday Wishes Expert website, you have been asked to provide your name, e-mail address, username, and password.

On some pages of Birthday Wishes Expert, you can submit ideas, make comments and requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are your name and e-mail address.

Any ideas you may submit, including text, photo and video become the property of Birthday Wishes Expert. Please read carefully the Terms and Conditions prior to submitting your ideas.

As a user of our website, you may request that we export and send you all the data we keep about you or that we delete all your data on our server. (see 11)

Certain information we collect is non-personal (see 4) and may not by itself lead to an identifiable person, but could become personal information when combined with other information. Examples of that non-personal information include your IP address and your GPS location.

We have no access to the missing information that would lead to an identifiable person. However, we might be legally obliged to disclose non-personal information to government authorities or confidentially to legal counsels of our website, in cases like the enforcement of the law by electronic crime services or through court orders, the exercise of our legal rights, the protection of our website from an attack or the protection of our users, partners or collaborators as regards to any legal action.

### **4\. Anonymous/Non-Personal Information We Collect:**

When you visit the www.birthdaywishes.expert website, we automatically collect basic non-personal information (that doesn’t lead to an identifiable person) including the address of your internet service provider (IP address), the web page that directed you to our site (referring URL), your web browser software, your operating system, your screen resolution and other non-personal data about your computer, mobile device and internet connection, and the pages you visited while on the www.birthdaywishes.expert website, as well as the time you spent at our website.

### **5\. Why Collect Information Anyway?**

Collecting information on our website has clearly no intention of targeting anyone – quite the contrary. Ideally, we, as website owners and operators, would like to do the absolute best for you without having to keep data about you (unless you’d really like us to 😉 ).

However, this is impossible. Anonymous data help us create the best content for our users, and even more. They help us make conclusions through the process of statistical data in order for you to get what you came for in the first place.

Data analysis is important to the improvement of our website’s content, find potential weaknesses and prevent fraud. It helps keep the site in operation and provide customer service and support.

Your preferences and subscription data help us communicate with you and they show us what you like so that we generate more of that.

### **6\. Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.birthdaywishes.expert does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the users access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

To read more information about browser cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### **7\. Log Files**

Like many other websites, www.birthdaywishes.expert makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

In order for our website to operate normally, the non-personal information we keep in log files is by default shared with our web hosting provider whose server we use.

### **8\. The Way We Use Information**

We use non-identifying and aggregate information (non-personal) to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell a service or an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We only use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Finally, we never disclose or share personal information, but there are cases where we might be legally obliged to disclose non-personal information when it comes to law enforcement (see 3).

### **9\. Third Party Advertising**

We also use third party advertisements on www.birthdaywishes.expert in order to financially support the site. Some of these ads might make use of tools such as web beacons and cookies (see 6) that could potentially also send these advertisers certain information like the web browser you are using to visit the site, whether you have Flash installed on your system, your IP (internet protocol), or your ISP (Internet Service Provider). Personally identifiable information data, like name, address, e-mail, phone number or similar are NOT included unless you have provided that data yourself and have agreed to their use on other websites or platforms.

All our collaborating advertising agencies or networks enable you to opt out of the internet-based advertising they offer. This is a list of the advertising networks or other services we collaborate with or use and the options you have as a user:

  * **Google** (through its products, services and companies including but not limited to YouTube, Google+, Google Photos, Google Fonts) makes use of the DoubleClick cookie to enable it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to www.birthdaywishes.expert and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads settings manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). When you use features that are connected to Google’s products and services while you are logged into accounts on platforms belonging to Google (like an embedded YouTube video while logged into YouTube or a Google+ button when you are logged into your Google account), anonymous data is collected. To make sure you know what data of yours is collected and change your preferences, visit [Google’s Privacy Checkup](https://myaccount.google.com/privacycheckup).
  * **Google Analytics** uses cookies to help us anonymously analyze how people use Birthday Wishes Expert.  It uses these cookies to identify anonymous interest data, provide anonymous demographic data from visits to Birthday Wishes Expert and other sites on the Internet, and to display advertising to returning visitors to this site. Users may opt out of the use of the Google Analytics cookie by visiting the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
  * **Third party vendors** , including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to www.birthdaywishes.expert. You may also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).
  * **Media.net** , another advertising network we collaborate with, also uses cookies to identify anonymous interest data, provide anonymous demographic data from visits to Birthday Wishes Expert and other sites on the Internet, and to display advertising to returning visitors to this site. If you would like Media.net not to use any data collected by its cookies to influence or personalize your Media.net ads, you can [opt-out here](https://www.media.net/en/adchoices).
  * **Amazon** , who we collaborate with, uses cookies to identify and collect anonymous user interest data on Birthday Wishes Expert and to display ads to its users. You may opt-out of Amazon’s collection of by visiting the [Amazon Advertising Preferences Opt-out](https://www.amazon.com/gp/dra/info).
  * We use **Pinterest** “Save” button (Pin it) and Pinterest social widgets for our users to interact with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc. For information about Pinterest and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy) and its [Personalization and data policy](https://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data).
  * We use **Twitter** Tweet button and social widgets and Twitter social widgets for our users to interact with the Twitter platform provided by Twitter, Inc. For information about Twitter and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy).
  * We use **Google+** “+1” (G+ button) for our users to interact with the Google Plus (Google+) platform provided by Google Inc. For information about Google +1 button and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
  * We use **YouTube** button and YouTube social widgets for our users to interact with the YouTube social network provided by Google Inc. For information about YouTube and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
  * We use **YouTube** video widget (embeded YouTube videos), a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. For information about YouTube and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
  * We use **Facebook** Like button and Facebook social widgets (Facebook, Inc.) for our users to interact with the Facebook platform provided by Facebook, Inc. For information about Facebook and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).
  * We use **CloudFlare** as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by CloudFlare Inc. The way CloudFlare is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about CloudFlare and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).
  * We use **Stackpath** as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by StackPath LLC. The way Stackpath is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about Stackpath and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.stackpath.com/privacy-statement/)
  * We use **KeyCDN** as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by proinity LLC. The way KeyCDN is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about KeyCDN and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.keycdn.com/privacy)
  * We use Google **reCAPTCHA** as a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to Google’s [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [terms of use](https://policies.google.com/terms).
  * We use a plugin called **AKISMET** as a SPAM comment protection service provided by Automattic. The use of AKISMET is subject to its [privacy policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

### **10\. Social Media Buttons and Third Party Websites**

On Birthday Wishes Expert we have included links to other websites or apps for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites or the way they use your personal information. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these websites or apps might differ from our own.

Birthday Wishes Expert also offers you the ability to interact socially with other users through the use of social buttons or plugins. Although we make our own plugins, these social media sites, such as Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter and Google+, may receive anonymous data when you click on their respective buttons. Even more, if you are a registered user of and logged into such social media sites, the personal information you have provided to those sites may be used by them to identify you on Birthday Wishes Expert.

### **11\. How You Can Correct or Erase Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in any personally identifiable information by sending us a request that clearly and credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

As a user of our website, you may request that we export and send you all the personal data we keep about you or that we delete all your personal data on our server.  If you’d like to do so, please [contact us](https://www.birthdaywishes.expert/contact-us/).

### **12\. Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### **13\. Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We do not require that children submit any personally identifiable information to use our website, play games or access special features.

If children submit ideas via e-mail, we ask for only the child’s first name (or nickname) and city, in order to identify contest winners. We will only use the e-mail address provided to respond to the child’s submission. It will not be used for any other purpose or sold or distributed to third parties. For videos and photos submitted, please do not show the child’s face or provide any other identifying information.

### **14\. Hosting of this Website**

This website is currently hosted in the United States and operated in the EU.

### **15\. Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of www.birthdaywishes.expert then you may [contact us](https://www.birthdaywishes.expert/contact-us/).

### **16\. How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by visiting [our contact page](https://www.birthdaywishes.expert/contact-us/).

**Last updated on:** May 24, 2018.

Please check this Privacy Policy periodically, as we may modify it occasionally.
